A Guide to the Records of the Office of the Vice President for Administration, Stuart K. Cassell, 1945-1975
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- 1963
  - Forestry, USDA, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Geological Science, 1963, Dr. Bryan N. Cooper-Head, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Golf Course- Brandon Glover, Manager, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Hardy, J.E.- Dormitory Manager, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Harper, Laura Jane- Dean of Home Economics, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Hieronimus of Roanoke, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Highway Department, State, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Housing, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Housing Police-Student, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Industrial Planning and Development, Division, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Irving, Dr. E.R.- College Physician, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - JK- Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Johnston, G. Burke- Dean School of Science and General Studies, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - King, Howard P. Jr.- Director Food Services, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - L-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Library, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - M-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Marion College, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Mc-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - McCormick Endowment Fund, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Meade, H.F., Resident Inspector, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Military, Air Force ROTC- Col. Ray W. Koontz, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Military, Army ROTC-Col. Col. T.M. Larner, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Military, Commandant of Cadets, Gen. M.W. Schewe, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Mitchell, H.H.- Dean School of Business Administration, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Monthly Statement of Revenue other than from Appropriations, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - NASA- Community College, Wallops Station, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - NASA Reports, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - National Science Foundation, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - O-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - O'Connell, Fred E.- Chief Accountant, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - P-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Physics Department- Dr. J.A. Jacobs, Head, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Poultry Husbandry Department- Dr. C.E. Howes, Head, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - President- Dr. T.M. Hahn, Jr. (2 folders), 1963 (Box 13, Folder 63-64)
  - Printing Department, F.O. Shanks, Manager, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Purchasing Agent- H.W. Swink, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Questionnaires (2 folders), 1963 (Box 13, Folder 67-68)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Radford College, Dr. Chas. K. Martin, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Review Committee- Student Classification and Assignment, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Row, Dr. S.B., Director of Community Colleges and Extension Programs, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - S-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - SACUBO(Southern Association of College and University Business Officers, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Scholarships, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sowder, Allen-Attorney, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Speech Material, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - State Auditor of Public Accounts- J. Gordon Bennett, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - State Board of Education, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - State Bureau of Property Records and Insurance, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - State Comptroller, Sidney C. Day Jr., 1963 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - State Council of Higher Education (2 folders), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
  - State Department of Purchases and Supplies, G. Lloyd Nunnally, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - State Director of Personnel, Dr. John W. Garber, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - State Director of the Budget- L.M. Kuhn, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - State Insurance Advisory Board, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - State Treasury Department, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Student Affairs-Dr. James W. Dean, Director (3 folders), 1963 (Box 14, Folder 17-19)
  - Student Aid Association, H.M. McEver, Director, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Summer Conference Schedule, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - T-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Tailor Shop-W.W. Dobyns, Director, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Tax Information- To Be Carried Forward, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - U-V Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C.-Planning Engineer, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Veterans Administration, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Tech Festival Association, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Vocational Education Department-Dr. Rufus Beamer, Head, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Worchester, W.G. Dean, School of Architecture and Engineering, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Wytheville Branch College, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - 1964-1966 Budget Material, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Committee-Traffic, Carried forward, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Budget Material, 1963-1964 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Salaries Faculty, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- 1964
  - Abbitt, J.R.-Director of Buildings and Grounds, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Academic Council Meeting, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Admissions-Directors Dr. Paul H. Farrier and Dr. M.P. Lacy, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Admissions-Reports, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station- Dr. H.H. Young, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Extension Service-Mr. W.H. Daughtry, Director, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Agronomy Department, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Airport-Mr. T.F. Broce, Manager, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Allotments From Richmond- Quarterly Allotments Estimates, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Association-Mr. Marcus Oliver, Secretary-Treasurer (2 folders), 1964 (Box 14, Folder 44-45)
  - Animal Husbandry Department-Mr. George Litton, Head, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Appalachian Power Co.-Corning Plant Hines, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Athletic Association, Mr. F.O. Moseley, Director, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Auditor's Reports, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Bank Correspondence, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Bell, Wilson B.- Dean of Agriculture, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Blanket Letters, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Board of Visitors, 1964 (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Board of Visitors- Financial Statements, 1964-12-31 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Boone, J.F.- Treasurer, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Brandt, Dr. Warren W.- Vice President (2 folders), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
  - Bull, Dr. Fred, Director- Engineering Experiment Statement, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Capital Outlays- July 1, 1964- June 30, 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Cato, W.H.- Director Guidance and Placement, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Chemistry Department-Dr. R.C Krug-Head, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Coliseum- Sound System, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Community College, Clifton Forge-Covington (2 folders), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
  - Community College- Danville, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Community College- Roanoke Technical, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Roanoke Technical Institute- To be carried forward, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Community College- Wytheville, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Committee- Alumni Homecoming, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Council of Presidents- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Committee- Commencement, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Committee- Homecoming, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Mineral Research Laboratory Committee, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Committee- Tech Festival, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Contract Correspondence- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Commission on Higher Education- Study of Higher Education in Virginia, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Conference on Continuum Mechanics- National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Contractors- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Cooperative(Co-op) Program- H. Stuart Smith, Director, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dairy Science- Dr. G.C. Graf, Head of Department, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - DeBusk, C.F.- Heat and Power, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Dean Burchard, Charles- Architecture, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Dean Harper, Laura J.- Home Economics, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Dean Johnston, G. Burke- Arts and Sciences, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Dean Mitchell, H.H.- Business Administration, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Dean Worcester, W.G.- Engineering, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Dean of Students, Dr. James W. Dean, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Dean of Men- J. Gordon Brown, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - F- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Fabian, Craig- Director of Development and Public Relations, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Federal Graduate Fellowship Program- Carried forward (3 folders), 1964 (Box 15, Folder 43-45)
  - Federal Aid to Higher Education-Title I, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Higher Education Facilities Committee-Title I, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Ford Foundation- Carried forward, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Geological Sciences- Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head of Department, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trusts, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Hahn, T. Marshall, Jr.- President (4 folders), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 10-13)
  - Hardy, J.E.- Director of Housing, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare- Department of, Washington D.C., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Highway Department- Right of Way, Steeles Tavern, Virginia, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Housing-Campus, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - IBM- Mr. Glen Justice, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Industrial Department, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Infirmary- Dr. E.R. Irvin, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - J-K Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - King, Howard, P, Jr.,- Director of Dining Halls (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - L- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Laundry- Mr. B.C. Anderson, Management, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Library, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Lunsford Sons and Izard, Chas., 1964 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Mc- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Marion College, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Military- Commandant, General M.W. Schewe, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Military- Air Force ROTC, Colonel J.R. Finton, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Military- Army ROTC, Colonel T.M. Larner, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - N- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration(NASA), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - National Science Foundation, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - N and W Railway Hearing-(4 folders), 1964-06-23 (Box 16, Folder 37-40)
  - O- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - O'Connell, Fred E.- Chief Accountant, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Personnel Applications (3 folders), 1964 (Box 16, Folder 43-45)
  - Personnel Applications- Internal Auditor, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Physics Department, Dr. J.A. Jacobs, Head, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Poultry Husbandry Department, Dr. C.E. Howes, Head, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Printing Department- F.O. Shanks- Manager, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Norfolk and Western, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Property Listing, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - R-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Radford College-Dr. Charles K. Martin, President, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Research Park, 1963-1964 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Row, Dr. S.B.- Director of Community Colleges and Extension Programs, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - S- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Salaries-Faculty (2 folders), 1964 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
  - Scholarships, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Sowder, Anthony- Attorney, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Attorney-State, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts, State- J. Gordon Bennett, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Budget-State Division, L.M. Kuhn, Director, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Comptroller-State, Sidney C. Day, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Higher Education-State Council of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Insurance Advisory Board- State, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Personnel- State Director of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Purchases and Supplies- State Department of, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Television-Advisory Council on Educational, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Treasury Department-State, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Statement of Revenues Other Than from Appropriations-Monthly, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Student Aid Association, H. M. McEver, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Student Correspondence, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - T- Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Town of Blacksburg, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Tailor Shop, W.W. Dobyns, Director, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Veterans Administration, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Veterinary Medical Students, University of Georgia, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - W-Miscellaneous, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Water Authority, Blacksburg/Christiansburg, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C.- Planning Engineer, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Non-Faculty Salary Adjustments-To be carried forward (2 folders), 1964 (Box 21, Folder 47, Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Purchasing Agent, Swink H.W., 1964 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Highway Department Right-of-Way, Steeles Tavern VA, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Financial Reports, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- 1965
  - Public Relations- Craig Fabian, Part 1, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Public Relations- Craig Fabian, Part 2, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Public Relations- Craig Fabian, Part 3, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Publications and News- Warren Strother, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Q- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - R- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - O- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - P- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Pending, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Personnel-State Division of, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Accountant-Chief, Carl Burke, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - A- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Abbitt, J.R. Director- Building and Grounds Department, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Academic Council, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Admissions-Report, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, W.H. Daughtrey, Director, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station, Dr. H.N. Young, Director, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Aircraft, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Airport, T.F. Broce-Manager, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Allotments from Richmond, Quarterly Allotment Estimates, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Alumni Association, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Art Commission, A. Edwin Kendrew, Chairman, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Athletic Association, F.O. Moseley-Director, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Attorney-State, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Auditor's Report, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Auditor of Public Accounts- J. Gordon Bennett, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - B- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Bank Correspondence, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Blanket Letters, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Board of Visitors, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Bonds, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Boone, J.F. Treasurer, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Brandt, Dr. Warren W- Vice President, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Purchases and Supply-Department of, G. Lloyd Nunnally, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Property Records and Insurance- Bureau of, Stewart R. Moore, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Public Relations, Craig Fabian, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Budget, Division of, L.M. Kuhn (2 folders), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Bull, Dr. Fred-Director Engineering Experiment Station, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Cassell, S.K.- Personal, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Cato, Dr. W.H. – Director Guidance and Placement, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Committee-Christ Kraft Program, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Committee-Homecoming, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Committee-Tech Festival, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Committee- Virginia Associated Research Center (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Community College-Clifton Forge, Covington, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Community College-Danville, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Community College-Roanoke Technical, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Community College-Wytheville, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Computing Center-Carried forward, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Contract Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Contractors-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cooper, Dr. Byron N.-Department of Geological Sciences Head, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Council of Higher Education-State (4 folders), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 19-22)
  - Dean of Men, Dr. J. Gordon Brown, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Dean of Students, Dr. James W. Dean (3 folders), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 24-26)
  - Dean of Students, Dr. James W. Dean (3 folders), 1966 (Box 18, Folder 27-29)
  - E- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - East Tennessee Natural Gas Company, 1964 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Evans, E.B.- Director of Personnel, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Fireworks on Campus, Display of, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Governor, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Golf Course, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Hahn, Dr. T. Marshall Jr.- President (5 folders), 1965 (Box 18, Folder 37-38, Box 19, Folder 1-3)
  - Row, Dr. Stuart- Director of Community Colleges and Extensions, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Harly, J.E.- Director of Student Housing, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, Department of- National Institutes of Health, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Heat and Power, C.F DeBusk and C.C. McCoy, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Heironimus of Roanoke, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Highway Department (2 folders), 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Housing-Staff, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - J-K Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - I-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - King, Howard P. – Director of Dining Halls (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - L- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Land Grant Colleges, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lunsford, Chas. Sons and Izard Insurance, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - M- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Mc- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Marion College, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Military- Army and Air Force ROTC, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Military- Commandment, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - N-Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - National Institutes of Health Project- Anaerobic Bacteria, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Shanks, F.O. – Manager, Printing Department, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Sowder, Allen-Attorney, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Statement of Revenues other than from Appropriations, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Water Authority, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Town of Blacksburg (3 folders), 1965 (Box 19, Folder 29-31)
  - Treasury-State Department of, Frank B. Miller, Assistant Treasurer, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Student Aid Association, H.M. McEver, Secretary, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Lunsford Sons and Izard, Charles, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Vandenberg, H.P.C.- Planning Engineer, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - SACUBO, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Scholarships, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Biennial Budget Material-1966-68, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Committee-Traffic, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Purchasing Agent, Swink H.W., 1965 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Salary Faculty, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- 1966
  - S- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - A-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Academic Council, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Accountant- Chief, Mr. Carl Burke, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Admissions- Dr. M.P. Lacy, Director, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Admission-Reports, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Agriculture Experiment, Dr. Coyt Wilson, Director, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Agriculture Extension Service, Dr. W.E. Skelton, Director, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Agronomy Department, Dr. H.L. Dunton, Head, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Airport-Mr. T.F. Broce, Manager, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Allocations, Supplementary, end-of year, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association, Phil R. Oliver, Senior Manager, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Applications, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Athletic Association, F.O. Mosely, Director, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Auditor's Report, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - B- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Bank Correspondence, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Blanket Letters, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Board of Visitors, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Boone, F.J., Treasurer, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Brandt, Dr. W.W., Vice President, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Buildings and Grounds-W.M. Sterrett, Director, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - C- Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Cassell, Stuart K.- Personal, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cato, Dr. W.H.- Guidance and Placement, Marcus L. Oliver, Associate, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Committee Commencement, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Committee-Governor's Day, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Community College-Clifton Forge-Covington, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Community College, Danville, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Community College-Roanoke Technical, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Community College-Wytheville, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Community Services Program, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Computing Center, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Contract Correspondence, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Contractors-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Homecoming Committee, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Visiting Scholar Committee, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Cooper, Dr. Byron N., Head of Geological Sciences, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Counseling Center, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - D-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Dean Wilson B. Bell, College of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Dean J. Gordon Brown-Dean of Men (2 folders), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 35-36)
  - Dean Fred W. Bull, Graduate School, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Dean Charles H. Burchard-College of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Dean of Students-Lists and Reports (2 folders), 1966 (Box 20, Folder 39-40)
  - Harder, Dean Martha, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Dean Laura Jane Harper, College of Home Economics, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Harrison, William B., Dean- Research Division, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Dean L.F. Malpass, College of Arts and Sciences, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Dean H.H. Mitchell, College of Business, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Skelton, W.E.-Dean of Extension and Director Cooperative Extension, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Dean W.G. Worcester, College of Engineering, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Dobyns, W.W.-Manager of Tailor Shop, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - E-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Evans, E.B. –Director of Personnel, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - F-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Fireworks on Campus- Display of, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - G-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Grants-Gifts, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Gifts-Dr. Huston St. Clair, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - H-Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)